e
e e
uh
Sunil yes Mr
Ashley Dr Ashley am I audible yes yes
you are audible uh who should I make the
co-host uh just make me the co-host I'll
be sharing the presentation and uh some
people from ICC will be elaborating
it okay I've made it the co-host uh I'll
will stop the sharing can you stop the
share yeah one moment yeah
Sunil is it okay can you share one one
moment yeah
fin Saturday Sunday Monday continuous
program
whenever you you ready you can start
yeah have one moment
I'm not getting the option to share it's
in the phone
actually you can maybe uh exit and
reenter okay
Sunil I can see
two
uh two times your name being
listed Sunil can you hear me
I can't hear you
Sunil yeah I can hear you now okay I
could hear you for a bit went off
again on phone actually yeah now
probably I'll have to log out from
computer one
moment yeah that'll be better you got
two two usern names
okay I'm again leaving and entering
again okay
okay Sunil I have made you co-host now
can you
unmute just allow me one more minute
yeah
spe
yeah we can see your screen now Sunil
okay let me check the
is the presentation visible yes yes very
much
yes yes it is visible you can make it
full screen if you want okay this is
also
fine yeah you got it
now okay one moment
so uh good afternoon everyone uh this is
Sunil
pal uh I welcome you all on this uh
bright
afternoon just a perfect uh environment
to know about the IC Lombard health
insurance uh we have uh with us Mr Vu
sha and Mr shes from ICI they have been
long Associated and have in-depth
knowledge of company as well as the
industry and they are the masters of the
plan so we have also with us vikas
vardan G uh he is providing support to
us and uh the coordinating Point uh with
IC Lombard so they'll be assisting us
and uh take you through to our today's
session so Mr vush and Mr Sur over to
you
please yeah thanks Sunil this is Sur and
am I
audible yes very
much yeah so thanks Sunil for the warm
introduction of me and my colleague
Sunil and Vias and I welcome all of you
to this webinar of icsu Lombard health
insurance and uh Sunil just for a quick
check so the communication mode will be
English Hindi or mix uh it will purely
English purely English okay that's good
good so uh see the entire uh this
presentation of icsa Lombard health
insurance so we'll talk about first you
know why health insurance and so
whenever you meet the customer so there
are certain pitch you need to make to
sell the health insurance so what is
going to be that pitch initially and
then about our vibrant Chi 2.0 plan
which we have recently launched so this
plan will be uh will Vu my colleague
will walk you through about the all the
salian feuture of this plan right so
without wasting any more time uh we'll
start with the fact of health insurance
so so my dear friends I think you know
that these are challenging time that we
are going through we are witnessing very
challenging and unprecedented time and
uh all of us are restricted in our home
and taking care of a lot of precautions
you know because of this covid pandemic
and uh lot of turbulence has happened in
the in the in the industry lot of
Industries have have been affected but
blessing and disguise I want to tell you
one thing that many Industries have seen
the downturn during this pandemic but
there is one industry or rather there is
one segment which has gone up and which
is going up month by month which is the
health insurance so if you look at the
health insurance
trajectory uh this year it has grown by
70 to 80% so I'm not talking about ICS
Lombard but if you talk about the entire
industry of health insurance it has
grown by 70 to 80% over last year why
because of the the pandemic Bing in
Disguise the customers are gradually
becoming aware about the need of health
insurance and uh in fact our Channel
partner conversion is also going up so
you know as many customers you approach
believe me your conversion will go very
very high so these are the time where I
think everybody should buy the health
insurance and these are the time where a
very good opportunity for you to reach
out to all the customer and convert them
into health insurance so I think this
opportunity we should not miss at all so
continue from here I want to tell you
about certain facts of health insurance
so why customer especially in India why
consumer should take health insurance
plan right and what are the benefit of
health insurance plan and then my
colleague Vu will take you through about
uh the the the product that we have in
health insurance so uh next slide I the
next to this okay if you look at this
health fact if you look at this slide
only three% Indians have their personal
health cover now this is not the data
which has been published by Lombard it
is as for the nsso health survey which
is a very famous Health company so in as
for this survey 80% of Indians are not
covered under any health insurance plan
and this is the biggest worry and
the way the medical inflation is going
up the medical inflation is going up 10%
yearly consistently so the treatment
that used to cost you three lakh rupees
you know a few years back it's costing
now 6 lakh rupees or 7 lakh rupees so
the way inflation is mounting up but in
today's time it's still 80% of Indians
are not covered and only
18% so in this 18% the government funded
are 12% only so only 18% of the urban
population and 14% of the rural
population is covered under any form of
health insurance so you can look at the
potential you can look at that is a
completely dment territory there is huge
to be done and and in the next 6 to
seven years or in the next 10 years you
will see that this industry is bound to
grow with a CH of more than
25% so these are some of the facts you
know that only 80% of Indians are only
20% of indents are covered and out of
20% only 5 to 6% IND are adequately
covered next
slide now this is a very interesting
slide which I think whenever you meet
customer you must speak that it has been
seen as per the survey that 1/4 of the
rural household it means 20% of the
rural household and 20% of urban
families in India are forced into debt
so whenever they come across with any
unforced circumstance whenever you know
they get hospitalized So 20% in case of
urban population and 25% in case of
rural population they have to either
borrow the money from their friends or
you know take the loan from the bank to
pay their medical bills so they are
forced into huge debt and some sometimes
they have to sell their asset also to
meet the hospitalization need so if you
look at this slide how household income
so so 65 to 68% rural customers whenever
they meet this kind of exigency or they
get hospitalized so they utilize their
65 to 68% household income they do not
have Medical cover and because of this
they are forced to take the money from
their saving or from their household
income so this ratio as far as the rural
population is concerned it is 65 to 68%
and uh uh you know borrowing from
friends and relative so around 23 to 20%
population they take the money from or
they borrow the money from their fan
relative and if you look at the urban in
urban also the same ratio Works 68 to
75% money you know they utilize from
their savings and 12 to 18% money they
have to borrow from their friends and
relative so these are the hardcore
health facts which I think you have to
make the customer aware that sir these
are the survey and basic survey I'm
telling you these are the facts so
obviously why you save the money
obviously you save the money for your
you know children marriage for your
children education for your retirement
for your uh you know or you want to
build a house you want to take a car you
want to go on the Leisure trip so there
are various dreams a person envis us and
because of these dreams a person save
the money now if any unforeseen event in
terms of medical hospitalization happens
in their life and if they they don't
have the medical cover so obviously they
are going to face a huge dent in their
saving now obviously what we do now we
come as a safeguard and we protect their
saving there somebody ask you what is
your role or somebody ask me what is my
role you know in terms of I'm sing the
health insurance what is my role so my
first role is to protect the saving of
my
customer yeah please come to the next
slide
well so if you look at there are certain
facts you know which I want to share
with you uh customers sa money to meet
personal Milestone so OB this slide I
think I've discussed to pay for their
child high education to arrange for
their son daughter marriage to buy a
property or inovate their existing
property vacation with the family so all
these things all these dreams a customer
or a normal person now save the money
for but because of the major illness
because of some accident because of some
major hospitalization because of the
illness all these savings get ered and
because of this there is a dent on the
goal that person has
taken yeah next
slide okay before this I think there are
certain Health fact which I want to tell
you before this slide there is a myth in
the market I'm sure whenever you go and
meet the younger customer so you you are
you are going to get the excuse from
their side I'm too young you know I
don't need any health insurance so once
once I turn 50 or more than 50 then I'll
need the health insurance but I want to
tell you some facts that in the last two
years last two years believe me those
who are below 50 years the claim from
those who are below 50 years were more
than those who are above 50 years so the
customers who are who you know whose age
were above 50 years have got the Lesser
claim than the customers whose age was
less than 50 years and because of
various reason so the reason is because
of the lifestyle disease because of the
stress and obviously the younger
generation they go out of their home to
do their job so they are more accident
prone you know second once illness
happens getting a life health insurance
cover in the future become difficult the
medical expenditure are the number one
reason for personal bankruptcy so now
this slide if you look at this slide
which is being uh shown here so health
insurance contribute 20% 27% of the
industry now this is again I want to
tell you that health insurance account
for 27% of The General insurance
industry and the Miracle happens this
year this year in The General insurance
industry usually the motor premium you
know always goes High the the ratio of
motor Premium Accounts for almost 60%
but this year it has
equalized because of the kind of health
insurance people are buying the health
insurance premium has gone health
insurance contribution in general
insurance industry has gone up so if you
look at this slide health is the second
largest segment in Indian Insurance
market after motor which has become the
now the primary segment and believe me
after one or two years you will see
health will even overcross the motor
segment the huge potential to grow
because uh uh in this line as I
explained you in the earlier slides only
20% customers are insured and out of 20%
only 5 to 6% are adequately insured so
there is used to
go
yeah now if you look at this Slide the
health insurance is growing as I told
you earlier also with the compounded
annual growth rate of
21% and as for the analyst as for the
Meeny and un report this health
insurance industry is going to grow with
the rate of 27% in the times to come so
27 to 30% this industry is growing you
know and over the next 5 years you will
see the similar growth so you can see
the huge amount of potential in this
industry huge amount of potential you
know in Indian market huge amount of
potential in health
insurance
yeah so these are couple of benefit
having the health insurance so I need
not reate because I'm sure you are the
master selling the health insurance but
these are couple of benefit first of all
is provide you peace of mind if you ask
me the first advantage of getting the
health insurance or adequate health
insurance is that it give me peace of
mind because I relaxed if I am having a
sufficient health insurance if something
unforeseen event happens yes I've got
the health insurance which can which can
take care of this so I've got a peace of
mind then the family health cover so my
entire family is covered then obviously
the tax benefit you get Advantage under
Section 1010 D you know for this health
insurance better and timely medical care
then Financial stability because if all
my personal
savings all my personal goals if all my
interest are safeguarded because I have
taken the health insurance so obviously
I financially stable because I know that
in any unforeseen time or if any
incident happens so I have health
insurance to take care of it I don't
have to erode my Financial saving for it
right so all these are the benefit of
having health insurance so money
management is important but it's not
limited to saving a investment alone
buying the right kind of health
insurance is an important step you know
that you should have
yeah so I think this is not the slide
for this segment I think we can skip
this
yeah right so uh now I would like to
invite venu you know for to further take
care of the product that we have so Vu
will Vu along with anoj my colleague
they will take you through about the chi
2.0 the Salient feature of the product
of ICS Lombard you know that we have so
over to you venu and
[Music]
anuch yeah V
are you
[Music]
there Mino are you
there anoj
I think both of them are not here in the
chat they're not there in the chat no no
come yeah they joined but
exited can you see them
suil are they are they logged in or they
logged
out uh they don't seems to be logged in
now yeah now he's joined v v joined yeah
Vu hello
Vu
V
mic yeah now now he's on I think v
v yes sir why you got disconnected know
what sir I tried many times but actually
uh I'm not able to get the U enter the
meeting it is again and again okay now
now now you have entered Vu and over to
you to describe the entire audience
about Chi
2.0
hello yeah you can go ahead you can hear
you uh hi Sur sir thank you so much uh
before uh V starts uh uh I want to say
something uh hello everyone good
afternoon myself Vishal shaso and I have
been working with IC Lombard from last
10 years in health agency vertical and
uh dad Garden branch is under my
supervision vision from last two years
uh first of all uh thanks to all of you
uh to make time for us today for this
session and I hope you and your loved
ones will be safe and will be taking all
the necessary
precautions as you all know why we are
gathered uh in this session today uh let
me little bit brief about the same uh as
a health agency vertical we have added
some new features to our product uh
which was in demand in the market for a
long time so if I'm talking about today
scenario uh ibard is a complete package
for your customers as now we have every
single features that exist uh in the
market with the competitions and uh uh
brand like IC Lombard is is a bigger
Edge for us uh so without taking much
time I would like to request vua to take
this forward session forward from
here thank you V thanks a lot and uh
good afternoon everybody my name is vua
I'm the part of the uh ICC Lombard
agency relationship team and I'm hope
that everybody is able to hear my voice
uh Vish PP is not
visible uh suril can you please do the
needful
uh yeah one moment uh there some problem
with the pp meanwhile you can uh just
give overview
meanwhile uh if the pp is available to
you uh I'll ask I'll request Dr Ashley
to make him co-host V shall I make you
cohost is that is that fine yeah no
issues
okay you can uh share your screen
M just hold
on velle you can share if you
like no I'm not able to do the same I'll
try and
then Sunil can you do
it uh I'm trying one moment
yeah we can see see your screen on
it yeah yeah PPT is will this PP will
do yeah yeah please go ahead okay okay
okay fair enough so uh as as I was
saying that and Vishal has already
quoted that our company has reintroduced
our top most selling product by the name
of chi that is complete health insurance
2.0 and uh we would be having the uh
best of best features which are
available in the industry uh Sunil G you
okay okay fair enough fair enough okay
uh so we would be added 10 new features
and four options with this particular
product and we would be having the
overview of those 10 options uh what
what detailed 10 options are giving the
benefit to the customer and uh what four
options which which this product is
having uh according to the customer need
customer can opt between these four
options and uh what all four options are
covering we will be having the overview
of that also so without taking much of
the time we just come on the add-on
coverages which has been re recently uh
reintroduced or they have recently added
to our Chi
2.0 so first benefit which has been
recently added it is unlimited reset
then air ambulance claim protector we
would be having the detail on these uh
benefits International coverages which
is by which is by the name of worldwide
coverage donor expenses is there
emergency assistance is there additional
samard protector is there domicillary
hospitalization is there super noaim
bonus is there and samard protector is
there so these are the 10
unique benefits which which exist in the
market and company has beautified these
benefit and added in the chi product and
if I talk about the uh chi options
available with the this product so we
are offering four options with with the
combination of these benefits only uh to
our customer under the head of chi only
so first option is our vanilla product
that is Health it is by the name of
Health Shield which is having uh which
is having the all the vanilla benefits
of this product and it is it is a non
OPD plan then we have the health Shield
plus that is the non OPD but it is
having a worldwide coverage that is the
international coverage and health Elite
is the OPD plus maternity benefit which
is having in the health Elite and with
the last option that is Health Elite
plus it is having OPD maternity and
international coverage it is having the
all the benefits which is which is
available with this particular product
Sunil G can you please change this slide
okay thank you thanks a lot so
now we would have a uh quick overview of
all the benefits which have been
recently introduced these five benefits
has been newly added they are not having
in our previous product so first benefit
is additional samard protector it says
if a customer is having a claim within
the particular policy year within the
limit of 50,000 it could be a single
claim or it could be a multiple
claims it's additional SU
benefit will remain intact it will not
be impacted in our Chi there is a no
claim bonus which which is which is
added on a yearly basis claim free year
and it would be 10% of your basic suot
and it will go up to 50% of the basic
sub short so if someone takes a claim of
Maximum up to 50,000 in a particular
year then we will not be decreasing his
incremental additional sumish short
which he has earned with the claim free
years so this is this is the benefit
with the additional samot protector if
if if this benefit this coverage is
included in your option second is claim
protector claim protector says I has
mentioned some of the uh non-- coverable
items which are excluding items uh which
all the industry is following so if the
customer get in the hospital and during
the hospitalization those items payment
is not paid by the uh insurance company
but if the customer has taken a CHI with
IC Lombard and he's having this option
available then the entire claim will be
settled including the exclusion list
also in this in this particular option
samish short protector is our inflation
benefit which we are offering to the
customer in regard to the inflation so
last year inflation rate the company has
taken it is 6% if uh in the current
policy year customer customer get the
renewal in his next year then he will be
had having the additional 6% of sard in
his Kitt for an example for an
example
hello okay uh for an example if customer
having a uh x amount of samish 10 lakh
Rupees of samish for that matter then
for the next financial policy year his
10 lakh Rupees samot would be the basic
samot and 6% of 10 lakh would be added
in his samard as as per the samish short
protector in regard to the inflation if
I talk about the fourth benefit that is
the worldwide coverage it is a very
beautiful benefit it gives you a
worldwide coverage uh we have a
international tribe with a TPA which is
providing the services to our customer
in in the worldwide um if the customer
uh uh opt for this then it is having a
benefit of if his basic Su is of 10 lakh
Rupees then he would be having equal to
his basic Su for worldwide coverage
benefit as well uh for an example if
he's having 10 lakh Rupees of basic suot
then the worldwide coverage is also is
equivalent to the basic submission but
that 10 lakh Rupees he or she can only
Avail the benefit under the head of
worldwide coverage only uh worldwide
coverage we are having two condition for
first condition is would be if the
customer is availing this benefit then
10% of co- payment will be there uh for
an example if he AVS the entire 10 lakh
Rupees of Sami then company will be the
claim comes with us for international
coverage in this particular option uh
the company will be paying his 9 lakh
rupees of settlement one lakh rupees
that that would be the 10% of his entire
claim amount has to be bearded by the
customer only there is another condition
for this the duration which in which the
the worldwide coverage will be active
that would be 45 days if a customer is
get hospitalized within the travel time
of 45 days then this benefit will be
offered if the it is more than if he has
uh completed 60 days or 65 days and
after that he got hospitalized this
benefit will not be giving any benefit
to the to the customer that that means
the the benefit of worldwide coverage is
limit to the 45 days only and it it
would be the customer he's traveling to
the particular country he got
hospitalized within the 45 days
only domicillary hospitalization our
fifth benefit which has been recently
added it says if a customer has been
suggested by the medical practitioner or
a hospital that you can move to your
home and get your further treatment
there only or in the condition if
Hospital says there is no room
availability to you have have to go uh
the treatment under the supervision of a
medical practitioner in your home only
so that is a case of domicillary
hospitalization if you have that option
available uh within your plan uh the
domicillary hospitalization experiences
will be taken care by ICC
logot uh so can you please okay thank
you so these are the features which are
uh already C old Chi was having but they
have been reintroduced with more
benefits the first benefit is super no
claim bonus it is an over and above
benefit which which we have already
discussed that Chi is having 10% of
additional Su short for every claim Fe
free year and it will go up to 50% and
super no claim bonus is over and above
this current benefit additional suard
benefit which says if your sumish short
is up to 10 lakh Rupees for every claim
free year your 50% of the basic suard
will be added in your SU
short and it will go up to the 100% of
the basic Su short that means for two
consecutive years if a customer doesn't
take any claim his 100% of the suard
will be added as a super no claim bonus
to his Kitty if his samard is up to 10
lakh Rupees but if his suard is 15 lakh
or it is above 15 lakh rupees then he or
she will be getting the benefit of 200%
maximum availed benefit will go up to
200% that that will be 505050 for each
every claim free year so this is the
benefit of super claim bonus in this
unlimited reset benefit previously we
are having the only one reset in the
policy year if the customer utilize the
entire amount so his entire basic subard
will be reinstated but now it is it is
having the unlimited option available uh
the reset will go as as many as time
within the policy year if the customer
utilize the entire some short amount but
the basic condition Remains the Same
that customer cannot Prevail the reset
benefit on the first claim of of that
policy year and second uh same person
same disease uh will not be considered
for the recent benefit then we have a
air ambulance coverage uh coverage
previously it was uh for the above 15
lakh rupees of samard and we are
offering the benefit of 50,000 per
member but now it is up to the limit of
the samish and it is unique in the
industry so this is the this is the uh
unique benefit which is company offering
in the head of air ambulance air
ambulance means if some excident happens
on mountain or some uh some ruler are or
some some uh like that area where the
road ambulance facility cannot be
provided then in that particular case in
the accident spot the uh there the
customer will be airlifted and he would
be hospitalized to the nearest hospital
in that particular so there there is a
cost involved in that so we as an
organization we are covering uh the
benefit of air ambulance up to the limit
of some short and uh fourth benefit is
our donor expenses previously we have
this donor expenses up to the limit of
50,000 and it it is an additional it is
an add-on benefit the customer has to to
pay extra to Avail this benefit but now
it is an inbu feature of our current
product by the name of donor expenses
and it will be up to the limit of 10
lakh Rupees so uh it says and it it is
also having a benefit that this 10 lakh
Rupees is over and above your basic Su
short benefit so if you have taken a
policy of for an example 10 lakh Rupees
then your donor expense will be separate
of 10 lakh Rupees so that means your
basic suard will be separate from your
donor expenses uh and in the last we
have the Emergency Services previously
we are just giving the domestic
ambulance offering uh for to our
customer for per event that the cost is
maximum to 1,500 rupees but now C
company has increased to 1% of the basic
sui or up to the maximum limit of 10,000
rupees per
accident so uh the the ambulance
roadside assistance has been increased
and you can Avail this benefit with app
I take care app you can just have the
facilitation over over the request over
the I take care app only assistance for
the ambulance it as I told you that
assistant for the ambulance has been
introduced with our I take care app it
is an very easy go and userfriendly app
by by that customer can Avail this
facility virtual consultation via audio
video or online portal we have the N
numbers of virtual consultation that is
tele consultation with the medical
practice
customer
or can opt or or any member of the
floater plan can opt for this uh option
virtual consultation via I take care app
only so this is the plan coverages uh
you can have the overview of the plan
coverages uh so if I talk about the
health Shield uh we are it is a non OPD
plan vanilla product uh if I talk about
the health Shield plus it is an non OPD
but it is having a worldwide coverage if
I talk about health Elite it is having
OPD and maternity both both benefits are
covered and if I talk about the health
Elite plus it is having all the three
benefits which is OPD maternity and
worldwide coverages if I talk about the
suot variation then shield and Elite is
having three lakh to 50 lakh rupees of
Sami shot and if I talk about the shield
plus and Elite plus it is having 15 lakh
rupees minimum s and maximum it can go
to 50 lakh rupees in patient treatment
definitely 24 hours of hospitalization
is mandatory for all the four plan
options pre and post off hospitalization
if I talk about the pre it is 30 days
for all all four options and post it is
for 60 days for all all the four options
if I talk about the iuse treatment I AA
yunani Sida and H Homeopathy treatment
the which would be in the during the
inpatient hospitalization treatment only
uh the benefit uh would be covered under
all the four options daycare process
procedure previously we are having
somewhere around 150 daycare listed dayc
carees which we are covering but now we
have covering all the dayc carees uh in
all the four options ped benefit if I
talk about we are having the lowest ped
benefit that is pre-existing disease
coverages we cover all the pre-existing
disclosed disease at the time of taking
the policy after the completion of two
years to CH there is a 24 months of
waiting period for an pay if I talk
about the additional submission benefit
that would be 10% of every claim year
will be added in your suard up to the
limit of 50% of your basic suard it
would be uh having the benefit for all
the four options wellness program is
there after earning certain amount of
points uh you can Avail the uh OPD
expenditure as an reimbursement basis
for per year you can earn the uh amount
of 2,000 rupes value added services are
available with all the four options free
heal checkup coupons if the it is a
individual plan one threee he checkup
cpon is offered and it if it would be an
floater plan two he checkup coupons
would be uh offered by ICC Lomar to our
customer at the time of taking the
policy and on the every renewal and and
uh these uh free heal checkup coupons
are availed with all the four options so
this is uh the overall plan benefits
which we have recently reintroduced with
our Chi so I think you would be having
uh little more clarity on the uh new
product that is chi 2.0 so V over to you
I think we can have a Q&A uh now if
somebody is having any query to please
feel free to ask we will be happy to
answer that uh thank you thanks a lot
over to
is Dr Ashley if anyone is having any
questions please
so will we get all these material with
us what showing or yes yes yes uh Ravi
sir will send you all the details okay
so what what we have planned is some of
us have wanted it in our local
language so what what I will do is I
will have a translation of this in the
next week itself
right right right I think after that I
can expect a lot of questions which I'll
put to
you yeah questions are very much
necessary to understand the plan and to
query the answers of the customers at
that very Point start
working I think there will be a lot of
questions what I feel right right right
right right so ICA has come up
very very attractive plans now uh there
were some features which we were missing
earlier but
uh with the launch of these four plans
no feature in the indust there is no
feature in the industry which is not
available in either of the plans so
whatever the customer needs is that can
be fulfilled through uh one of these
four plans out of these four plans which
are displayed now which is which two are
the know most frequently used or
taken well uh
as vui has already told us that Health
Sheed is the vanilla product the basic
product Health Sheed yes H sheet plus is
having a worldwide coverage attached to
it there are no OPD plans yeah if you go
to health Elite it has that uh Health
sheet plus the OPD benefits available
and health Elite plus is that basic plan
OPD and worldwide coverage so which is
having more upake now yeah the most
preferred one is still hell Shield the
first one the basic one right yeah if
you can see on the screen there are
cross marks against
claim question these these options are
available under add-ons Riders corre so
if we give the Riders as per the
customer choice this hell Shield becomes
uh one of its kind of product correct so
Sunil my question is if somebody opts
for health Shield
basic right then after some time they
decided that they want an upgrade is
that
possible uh vui if you can help on this
query
please uh Vu G or Vishal G Vishal G are
you
there yeah he's here he is
there okay uh sir
yeah the question is if somebody Ops for
health shield and then decides after 2
three months that they want that upgrade
is that
possible sorry pardon sir please repeat
your question if somebody has taken
Health Shield basic plan M but after 2
three months they decided that they want
Health sheet plus is that possible no
same will be happen at the time of
anniversary renewal
anniversary only during the yearly uh at
the time of renewal
only only during the renewal you can
change correct yeah he she can migrate
the same at the time of renal okay okay
so in between it is not possible no okay
okay thank
you is there any plan that allows any
other
upgrade sorry s didn't get you is there
any plan that allows a customer to
upgrade in between no sir there is
nothing in the industry like that
correct nothing only midterm additions
are allowed like spouse addition child
addition nothing more than it is not
followed in the industry also yeah
industry
practice fine thank you thank you thank
you sir I'm sorry little bit uh Network
issue is over here from my side well
that's okay I understood what you're
saying Sunil continue please you were
saying something
Sunil
Sunil Sunil can you hear
me I'm I'm able to hear you yeah so do
you wanted to say something more about
these
charts
okay in all these plant 10% co-pay is
applicable
correct sir at the time of worldwi
coverage the only at that that claims 10
10% copay is there in the normal
domestic uh uh basic suard utilization
at that particular time you do not have
any cop available yeah the entire the
entire amount would be cashless or it
would be in the reimbursement mode okay
okay and uh worldwide coverage has to be
a planned one I
believe it has to be a planned one it is
an optional cover
sir okay no the hospitalization has to
be planned it cannot be an emergency
exactly
exactly okay if if suppose the holder
travels abroad and he has a has a heart
attack it will not be covered
correct it depends
sir what kind of situation on that time
happens it depends
situation what kind of disease customer
has is any any other ped is there like
BP so that will be not cover if any
accident like if arises on that that
time that will be covered on that time
okay with the worldwide correct yeah
okay and Dr Ashley apart from that uh Mo
most of the time uh Travelers take
travel insurance while traveling abroad
add to yeah rather than availing the
benefit of this plan because there are
some conditions attached to it so it's
always better to take a travel insurance
while traveling abroad okay that is a
common
practice and and that travel insurance
is very cheap also so okay okay is that
also available in in our
platform yes yes very much available
okay thank
you is there anything else Sunil that
you want to add and then
summarize well uh we have been uh
promoting icac very strongly uh because
uh their after sales service part is is
best among the industry we have not
faced any uh whatsoever uh situation uh
where some awkward situation where we
are not able to help the customer we
have not faced any such situation in
that last 3 four years so we have been
promoting IC from the core of our heart
so this is our most preferred uh plans
okay and uh vikas is always there he's
very very helpful even in the late
nights or early mornings he's always
there whenever we need so service part
is very much guaranteed plus ICC Lombard
has already established themselves as
the best service providers in the
industry so their data speaks of
themselves
so and what data is reflecting we have
felt the same way so it's it's very good
I believe okay sounds really good sir
thanks for your kind
words uh any other questions uh
definitely we'll be having a separate
Q&A and Dr Ashley if you have any other
questions otherwise we can we'll wrap up
right right right so thank you so much
Sunil for this time and uh I want our
special team from icsa
Vish
mras thank you so much for sharing your
beautiful Saturday afternoon with
us right thank you so much sir thanks to
all for joining in and spare time with
us uh for this session and uh please be
safe be home and stay at home and happy
selling sir thank you so much for
joining in have a brilliant weekend
thank you thank you thank you everyone
thank
[Music]
you thank you
we'll see you tomorrow 10:00